All right, we'll call to order the MSU a meeting for Tuesday, May 5th, 2026
Public input unscheduled personal appearances. We have none
Three discussion possible action on 3a claims list
3b Tetra tech claim for Pensacola GRDA relicensing in the amount of
$13,786 and 25 cents. Yes, sir
So this is for some work that Tetra Tech has done in our relicensing. They've also done some work for us for
the highway 125
Road race information. Oh, so this is just that invoice for that
Three see minutes from the April 21st 2026 regular meeting
I
3d worker authorization to dash zero to six
With own engineering for water treatment plant piping motor and pump rehab construction administration and inspection
Not to exceed forty five thousand dollars there. Yes, sir
This is for just what it says for the water treatment plant where we approved for the construction down there this is for the
For them to for the construction services for them to oversee and inspect
It is an hourly it's by the hour so it's not to exceed 45,000 on this
This is budgeted
Make a motion we approve
Three e work authorization three dash
two zero to six with own engineering for highway 44 waterline crossing and
treaty road construction administration and inspection not to exceed
$25,000
Same type of work that they're doing they're inspecting that
materials the piping the boring the safety all that it has to do with those construction services and the billing portion that it's for
the
south of the water tower the new water tower on 69 a we're boring across and
That project that we awarded to accuracy underground to bore across the turnpike there. It'll feed if you guys remember
That's what feeds that's that second feed. We're gonna have to the east side of
Same deal it's an hourly
Make a motion we approve
Three F discuss the possible vote on
perpetual utility easement agreement with the Shawnee tribe for the installation and maintenance of a water line
Located near the new 69 a water tower including an all including
authorization of one time payment in the amount of
$5,000 and to authorize the trust manager to execute all necessary documents
Yeah, this is for that
More that we just talked about this is across the Shawnee tribe piece of property just out there
20-foot utilities
Water line across there for that. They they had their first read yesterday on that week suspect
They'll take it to their next
They have not approved they have not approved this shit either so what if you guys approve this tonight
We'll be able to take it to them if they approve it
We'll be able to get this easement that we need to get across the turnpike
I'll make motion approved
Second
3g 3g agreement with SEL engineering services incorporated for substation to upgrade for the protection
of the buses and transformers including design installation equipment and commissioning not to exceed
103,000
595 dollars
so we you guys approved here wall back a
to read to
Study on those relay settings at sub to there's two substation transformers there and in that when we did that they found that we
Did not have redundant
protection on those substation transformers in that bus and so subsequently they
Suggested that this is what we do
This is the work we do we will save some money if we do execute it now because they'll already be mobilized
They will do all that work at the same time when they're already here
Updating the settings that they have on those other relays plus they'll coordinate those two sets of
Settings together so we there's some cost savings by doing it at the same time
This also will come out of our electric budget
For other new business if any which has risen since the posting of this agenda
five staff reports
six trustee community announcements
Seven trust manager communications. Yes, sir